LEANDRO MATIAS LUNA

Software Developer

- @ sick_ace51@hotmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/leandro-matias-luna-a572731a5/

SUMMARY

I am a software developer with 1 year of experience in technologies: spring, mysql, hibernate, node, react, git, github. I have great leadership, innovation, problem solving, communication, organization and group motivation skills. I have developed and implemented rest microservices.

EXPERIENCE

Back End Developer

02/2023 - Ongoing

No-Country

Remote

ΙT

- Backend E-commerce Development: Java, Springboot, Hibernate, MySQL, Scrum Methodology, Dependency Injection, REST API, SOLID, Git, Github, Figma, Trello.
- I worked in communication with the front team for the development of ecommerce, using agile scrum methodologies with sprint and dailys.

Full Stack Developer

09/2022 - Ongoing

Freelancer

Remote

IT

- CRUD microservices Project Android/ionic: React-SpringMvn-Docker
- Portfolio React
- Backend E-commerce: Springboot, ApiREST, java, Hibernate, MySQL, OAuth, Stripe, Git
- Backend CRUD: Springboot, ApiREST, Hibernate, MySQL, Argon2, JWT
- Desktop Application SystemClients SQL, Java
- Desktop Application BMI Calculator- Java
- · Desktop Application Networking Java
- Scripts Bash/Unix
- · Web Scrapping Python
- Scripts/Automations Python

Backend Developer

12/2021 - 12/2022

Noventiq

Bsas, Argentina

ΙT

- Development of REST microservices e implementations.
- I worked in communication with the development team to implement microservices, develop them and fix bugs in production.

EDUCATION

Informatics Engineering 03/2020 - Ongoing

UADE

Udemy 02/2021 - Ongoing

Spring/Py/Java

Full-stack MERN 04/2023 - 06/2023

Nucba



LANGUAGES

English B1
Spanish Native

SKILLS

Programming ·

Spring / Hibernate / JPA ·

React / Node · MySQL/MongoDB ·

jUnit / Selenium · Linux / Bash ·

Python / Java / Javascript

STRENGTHS



Inspiring and guiding teams to achieve success.

Trategic Planning

Creating long-term plans for success.

★ Innovative Thinking

Developing new ideas and creative solutions.